<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FinalExer1</string>
    <string-array name="productNames">
        <item>Oracle Red Bull Racing 2022 Max Verstrappen World Champion Cap</item>
        <item>Red Bull Racing Max Verstrappen 2024 F1 World Driver\'s Champion Poster</item>
        <item>Red Bull Racing Max Verstrappen Expression Driver Hoodie - Orange - Unisex</item>
        <item>Red Bull Racing Max Verstrappen Puzzle Driver T-Shirt - Orange - Unisex</item>
        <item>red Bull Racing Max Verstrappen Dutch Grand Prix Collectors\'s Edition Poster - 2024</item>
        <item>Oracle Red Bull Racing Max Verstrappen Driver T-Shirt - Unisex</item>
        <item>Red Bull Racing Max Verstrappen Helmet Full Zip Hoodie - Unisex</item>
        <item>Red Bull Racing RB18 No.1 Winner Japanese GP 2022 - Max Verstrappen World Champion - 1:12 Model with Board</item>
        <item>Red Bull Racing New Era Team Cuff Beanie - Navy</item>
        <item>Red Bull Racing New Era Max Verstrappen 9SEVENTY Piped Cap - Navy</item>
        <item>Red Bull Racing 2024 New Era Sergio Perez 9FORTY Cap</item>
        <item>Red Bull Racing Graphic Bull T-Shirt - White - Unisex</item>
        <item>Red Bull Racing 2025 Team Full Zip Hoodie - Unisex</item>
        <item>Red Bull Racing Core Logo Polo - Navy - Unisex</item>
        <item>Red Bull Racing Core Logo T-Shirt - Navy - Unisex</item>
        <item>Red Bull Racing New Era Seasonal Repreve E-Frame Trucker Cap</item>
        <item>Red Bull Racing 2025 Team Polo</item>
        <item>Red Bull Racing Core Logo Polo - White - Unisex</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="productPrices">
        <item>15.00</item>
        <item>129.00</item>
        <item>85.00</item>
        <item>39.00</item>
        <item>103.00</item>
        <item>18.30</item>
        <item>91.00</item>
        <item>527.04</item>
        <item>42.00</item>
        <item>55.00</item>
        <item>14.64</item>
        <item>46.00</item>
        <item>137.00</item>
        <item>68.00</item>
        <item>39.00</item>
        <item>18.30</item>
        <item>101.00</item>
        <item>68.00</item>
    </string-array>
    <integer-array name="productImages">
        <item>@drawable/max_champion_cap</item>
        <item>@drawable/max_champion_poster</item>
        <item>@drawable/max_orange_hoodie</item>
        <item>@drawable/max_orange_shirt</item>
        <item>@drawable/max_poster</item>
        <item>@drawable/max_tshirt</item>
        <item>@drawable/max_white_hoodie</item>
        <item>@drawable/model_board</item>
        <item>@drawable/redbull_beanie</item>
        <item>@drawable/redbull_cap</item>
        <item>@drawable/redbull_cap2024</item>
        <item>@drawable/redbull_graphict</item>
        <item>@drawable/redbull_jacket</item>
        <item>@drawable/redbull_polo</item>
        <item>@drawable/redbull_shirt</item>
        <item>@drawable/redbull_truckercap</item>
        <item>@drawable/redbull_tshirt</item>
        <item>@drawable/white_polo</item>
    </integer-array>

    <string name="maxchampcap">
        Celebrate Max Verstappen\'s incredible back to back world championship victories with this Make It A Double cap.
        Featuring graphics displaying the years – 2021 and 2022 – that he brought home the winner\'s trophy, this is the
        perfect souvenir for fans everywhere to celebrate a moment of true F1 history.
    </string>

    <string name="maxchamppos">
        Immortalize Max Verstappen\'s four consecutive F1 World Drivers\' Championship titles with this incredible poster.
        Featuring stylish artwork of Verstappen and his car it evokes speed, determination and achievement, the perfect
        addition to any Formula One fan\'s space. The poster is a collaboration between Automobilist, Oracle Red Bull
        Racing, and Madebycito, created to celebrate Max Verstappen\'s 4th World Championship title. Due to the nature
        of Madebycito\'s graffiti-style artwork, minor variations may exist between the product image and the final poster.
    </string>

    <string name="maxorangehood">
        Get a warmer feel with this fantastic hoodie. The iconic F1 branding will make sure you have a great way to show off
        your support whatever the weather.
    </string>

    <string name="maxpost">
        Decorate your home in real racing style with this great F1 poster. This is the ideal way to showcase your love of
        everything about Formula One.
    </string>

    <string name="maxorangshirt">
        Wear the love of your chosen Team at any time. Everyone needs t-shirts so make sure yours is built with F1 precision
        and style.
    </string>

    <string name="maxtshirt">
        Show off your passion for the thrill of Formula One and the skill of the Red Bull Racing team with the official Driver
        Fanwear Collection. This tee features an \'MV1\' graphic and RBR team logo on the chest and a colour fade pattern for a
        distinctive but classic F1 look. The classic cut and comfortable fit make it great for everyday wear.
    </string>

    <string name="beanie">
        Top off your look with one of the biggest names in Formula One. Your loyalty will be on proud display with this hat that
        will carry your passion for F1 to new heights.
    </string>

    <string name="modelboard">
        Own a keepsake of an iconic part of the Formula 1 experience. A brilliant souvenir to remind you of classic moments, and
        a great decoration as well.
    </string>

    <string name="whitehood">
        Get a warmer feel with this fantastic hoodie. The iconic F1 branding will make sure you have a great way to show off your
        support whatever the weather.
    </string>

    <string name="redbullcap">
        Get the look of your favourite racing team. This iconic item will add some speed style to any other outfit and you can show
        off your allegiance whether trackside or anywhere else!
    </string>

    <string name="cap2024">
        Get set for the 2024 F1 season in unbeatable Red Bull Racing style with the official New Era team collection. This Sergio Perez
        cap features his car number 11 on the brim and a high structured crown, with an adjustable snapback closure for a perfect fit
        and an Oracle Red Bull Racing patch sewn to the front crown.
    </string>

    <string name="graphict">
        Wear the love of your chosen Team at any time. Everyone needs t-shirts so make sure yours is built with F1 precision and style.
    </string>

    <string name="redbulljacket">
        Show your support for Red Bull Racing right out of the gate as Liam Lawson joins Max Verstappen on the track for the 2025 season.
        This full zip hoodie features a straight cut through the body for a sleek and comfortable fit and features highly detailed team
        and sponsor branding on the chest, back and sleeves. The hood rounds out the silhouette while giving you extra warmth and cover
        when you need it.
    </string>

    <string name="redbullpolo">
        Feel like a bona fide member of the team in this stylish polo. This iconic garment is synonymous with the F1 image and will strike
        a great look any time.
    </string>

    <string name="redbullshirt">
        Wear the love of your chosen Team at any time. Everyone needs t-shirts so make sure yours is built with F1 precision and style.
    </string>

    <string name="truckercap">
        Keep the sun off and flaunt your style. This is the perfect way to stay cool and strut your stuff like a pro.
    </string>

    <string name="redbulltshirt">
        Show your support for Max Verstappen for every start, every pit stop and every chequered flag of the 2025 race season with this
        official Red Bull Racing tee. It features his name and car number on the chest, along with iconic Red Bull and Castore emblems
        and graphics for a team look you can proudly wear anywhere to show your allegiance.
    </string>

    <string name="whitepolo">
        Feel like a bona fide member of the Team in this stylish polo. This iconic garment is synonymous with the F1 image and will strike a great look any time.
    </string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>